[{
        "question": "Which of the following organelle is NOT part of an animal cell?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Nucleus",
            "b": "Cytoplasm",
            "c": "Cell membrane",
            "d": "Cell wall"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which answer gives the correct functions of both the cytoplasm AND the cell membrane?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "The Cytoplasm is the place where cell reactions take place. ‎ ‎ ‎The cell membrane controls what goes in and out of a cell",
            "b": "The Cytoplasm controls cell division ‎ ‎ ‎ The cell membrane gives support to the cell",
            "c": "The Cytoplasm gives support to the cell ‎ ‎  ‎ The cell membrane place where cell reactions take place",
            "d": "The Cytoplasm controls cell division ‎ ‎  ‎ The cell membrane controls what goes in and out of a cell"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these units is most suitable for measuring the length of a cell?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Millimetres",
            "b": "Micrometres",
            "c": "Terametre",
            "d": "Femtometre"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these cellular structures contain DNA?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Rough Endoplasmic Reticulum",
            "b": "Smooth Endoplasmic Reticulum",
            "c": "Lysosome",
            "d": "Mitochondria"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "All of the following organelle interact with ribosomes except... ",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Rough Endoplasmic Reticulum",
            "b": "Smooth Endoplasmic Reticulum",
            "c": "Mitochondria",
            "d": "Golgi Body"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "c",
        "topic": "ribosomes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are ribosomes made up of?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "RNA",
            "b": "DNA",
            "c": "DNA, and proteins",
            "d": "RNA and proteins"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a",
        "topic": "ribosomes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following statements are true?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Ribosomes are self-replicating organelle",
            "b": "Ribosomes have a double membrane",
            "c": "Ribsomes are coded by DNA",
            "d": "Ribosomes are coded by RNA"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "c",
        "topic": "ribosomes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is the Golgi stack the same as the Golgi cisternae?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "True",
            "b": "False"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b",
        "topic": "golgi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which organelle handles shipping and distributing of protiens and chemicals produced by the cell?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Mitochondria",
            "b": "Smooth Endoplasmic Reticulum",
            "c": "Lysosome",
            "d": "Golgi Body"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "d",
        "topic": "golgi"
    },
    {
        "question": "The region around the Golgi apparatus where other organelles are absent is called?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Zone of inhibition",
            "b": "Zone of exclusion",
            "c": "Zone of abscene",
            "d": "All of the above"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b",
        "topic": "golgi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pick the correctly matched pair?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Lysosomes - involved in synthesizing amino acids",
            "b": "Endoplasmic reticulum - plays a role in synthesising protiens and lipids ",
            "c": "Centrosomes - Provides enzymes for digestion",
            "d": "All of the above"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b",
        "topic": "golgi"
    }


]